best-prepaid-cell-phone-plans.com 2012-10-14

# Privacy Policy

| 

COMMITMENT TO YOUR PRIVACY  
Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. We want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.  
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

INFORMATION WE GATHER AND TRACK  
We gather two types of information about users:

  * Information that users provide through optional, voluntary submissions. These are voluntary submissions to receive our electronic newsletters, to participate in our message boards or forums, to email a friend, and from participation in polls and surveys
  * Information we gather through aggregated tracking information derived mainly by tallying page views throughout our sites. This information allows us to better tailor our content to readers' needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience. Because this site derives its revenue mainly from sponsorships and advertising, providing such aggregated demographic data is essential to keeping our service free to users. Under no circumstances do we divulge any information about an individual user to a third party. 

We Gather User Information In The Following Processes:

Optional Voluntary Information

We offer the following free services, which require some type of voluntary submission of personal information by users:

1\. Electronic newsletters policy (Dispatches)

We may offer a free electronic newsletter to users. We may gather the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the link provided in every newsletter that points users to the subscription management. 

2\. Message boards/forums policy

We may offer forums in the future. Users of the site's Forums must register for these services in order to post messages, although they needn't register to visit the site. 

3\. "E-mail this to a friend" policy

We may offer our site users the option to choose to electronically forward a link, page, or documents to someone else by clicking "e-mail this to a friend". The user must provide their email address, as well as that of the recipient. This information is used only in the case of transmission errors and, of course, to let the recipient know who sent the email. The information is not used for any other purpose.

4\. Polling

We may offer interactive polls to users so they can easily share their opinions with other users and see what our audience thinks about important issues. Opinions or other responses to polls are aggregated and are not identifiable to any particular user. We may use a system to "tag" users after they have voted, so they can vote only once on a particular question. This tag is not correlated with information about individual users.

5\. Surveys

We may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We sometimes share the aggregated demographic information in these surveys with our sponsors, advertisers and partners. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

Children

Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.

Usage tracking

We may track user traffic patterns throughout all of our sites. However, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users. We may break down overall usage statistics according to a user's domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user's browser).  
We sometimes track and catalog the search terms that users enter in our Search function, but this tracking is never associated with individual users. We use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

Cookies

We may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain Personal Information although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.  
You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you may need cookies to participate actively in any message boards, forums, polling or surveys offered.

##  _Privacy Policy Use_

USE OF INFORMATION

We use any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience in our network of sites, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the sites or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

As stated above, we may use information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters and to enable users to participate in polls, surveys, message boards, and forums. We may send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. We never share newsletter mailing lists with any third parties, including advertisers, sponsors or partners.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas. We do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you. We may track search terms entered in Search function as one of many measures of what interests our users. But we don't track which terms a particular user enters.

We create aggregate reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for advertisers, sponsors and partners. This allows our advertisers to advertise more effectively, and allows our users to receive advertisements that are pertinent to their needs. We don't track the usage patterns of individual users.

Some advertisements may be affiliate links. In this case, a cookie is set identifying the affiliate network and this website’s account with that network. Then if the user clicks or makes a purchase after clicking on a link from this website, the affiliate network is able to credit us with a commission.

We will not disclose any information about any individual user except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

SHARING OF THE INFORMATION

We use the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

OPT-OUT POLICY

We give users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * **Opting not to give feedback or to register to receive any electronic newsletters we may offer.**  

  * **Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas we may offer, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users**

YOUR CONSENT

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

| **Share this page:  **| |   
---|---|---  
  
Enjoy this page? Why not share it with others! Here's how...  
  
Hi, Thanks for checking out this site! Go to the menu on the left for the plan write-ups. From there you'll find links to the individual phone reviews as well as other topics. On many of the pages you can even contribute your own questions and reviews.Below you can take a look at some of the current offers.
